// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Don’t make a such a bother ………………… which dress to wear.",
    answer: "about",
    options: [ "about", "with","who","in" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: " The ship sank ……………………. the bottom.",
    answer: "to",
    options: ["to","at","with","in"]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question:"She spanked the boy ………………………. his bottom.",
    answer: "on",
    options: [
      "in", "at","on","to" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "In olden days the poor had to depend ……………………. the parish’s bounty.",
    answer: "on",
    options: ["with","on","over","at" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "He was punished ………………………. a boyish prank.",
    answer: "for",
    options: [ "for", "with","to","over" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "The typist botched the work and had to start …………………….",
    answer: "over",
    options: ["over", "out","on","above"  ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: " The guest speaker turned ………………………… to be a deadly bore.",
    answer: "out",
    options: [ "out", "up","in","on" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "The policemen showed great bravery …………………………. the face of danger.",
    answer: "in",
    options: [ "in", "on","at","above" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "We were stunned …………………………. the breadth of the mountain range.",
    answer: "by",
    options: [ "by", "with","of","on" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Mosquitoes breed ……………………….. stagnant water.",
    answer: "in",
    options: [  "into", "in","on","above"  ]
  },
    {
    numb: 11,
    question: "A storm is brewing ……………………… the horizon.",
    answer: "on",
    options: [   "on", "over","at","to" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 12,
    question: " Her bridal gown was ……………………… pure silk.",
    answer: "of",
    options: [  "from", "of","up","to" ]
  },
];